

## **SUMMARY**

Software engineer with full stack development experience including requirements gathering, design, coding, testing, and demonstrations. Patient mentor with a strong leadership drive who can use communication to achieve team goals. Always willing and excited to take ownership of teams and products to drive them towards success.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## Senior Software Engineer, Infor

St. Paul, MN — 2011-present

- Create web based, cloud deployed, ERP user interfaces using JavaScript, Node, jQuery, HTML5, and CSS in an agile environment.
- Senior developer on a team of associate and general level engineers.
- Certified mentor of four engineers.
- Responsible for the design and implementation of new features with a focus on speed, design, usability, and customer needs.
- Point of contact for multiple products used worldwide by hundreds of thousands of users.
- Work directly with customers to solve high priority issues.
- Give new feature presentations and live demos in front of hundreds of customers.
- Develop blog posts and videos to promote and generate excitement for products.

## Software Engineer, Quantum Retail Technology

Minneapolis, MN — 2011

• Developed supply chain management software using Java and an array of web technologies in an agile/scrum environment.

# Quality Assurance Engineer, Winona State University Software Testing and Development Lab

Winona, MN — 2010-2011

- Created a full coverage test plan to be used by future engineers.
- Searched for flaws in multiple products and documented them using bug reporting software.

## Teaching Assistant/Personal Tutor, Winona State University

Winona. MN — 2010-2011

• Met with individual students outside of class for additional assistance with problems, labs, or general topic understanding and assisted professors with weekly in-class labs.



# Senior Software Engineer

## **EDUCATION**

## Winona State University, BS Computer Science

Winona, MN — Graduated May 2011

#### **Relevant Courses**

- Algorithms and Problem Solving
- Computer and Network Security
- Object Oriented Design
- Software Engineering
- Web Programming

#### **Accomplishments**

- Dean's list five consecutive semesters
- Represented computer science department at admitted students' ceremony

## SKILLS

#### **Technical**

- Languages: JavaScript (ES6), CSS, HTML5, PHP, MySQL, XSLT, Java
- Tools used professionally: Node.js, Express, jQuery, Grunt, Babel, Selenium, Chai, QUnit
- Tools used personally: React, Angular, Webpack, Underscore/Lodash
- Object-oriented software design and development using scrum/agile methods
- Software testing and bug reporting

#### **Personal**

- Strong communication skills
- Persistent
- Self-motivated
- Problem solver
- Patient

### **HOBBIES**

- Toastmasters International [Vice President of St. Paul public club 7507]
- Personal programming projects, I enjoy keeping up on the latest frameworks [samples available upon request]
- Woodworking [www.thirdstallwoodworking.com; demonstrates technical writing ability]
- Reading
- Outdoor activities including cycling, golf, hiking, hunting, camping, fishing, and canoeing

### REFERENCES

Available upon request

14274 Bloomfield Ct. Rosemount, MN 55068

T: 507.402.6246 E: andy@awbuboltz.com